

Phi Khanh Do

Full-stack Software Engineer

💌 ngoisaomouoc555@gmail.com 🛛 🗣 Doc Mo 3, Gia Tanl, Thong Nhat, Dong Nai, Vietnam

About

I am an advanced full-stack developer with over 8 years of experience in structuring, developing and implementing interactive websites and applications.

I've experienced with all stages of development cycle for dynamic web projects.

I have strong communication and collaboration skills, and a desire to work as part of a team committed to a common goal.

I'm also a quick learner of new technologies and I still love to immerse myself in trending tech.

Employment

Front-end Web Developer

I always strive to exceed expectations.

Jul 2022 - Nov 2022

Impress + Pearshop

- As a front-end web developer, I have built two websites using vue.js, nuxt.js and strapi.
- Integrated the animations in pages using d3.js and added reusable components.

Full-stack Web Developer

Jul 2020 - Jun 2022

Hybrid

- Built GYM training website and implemented enhancements that significantly improved web functionality and speed.
- Actively contributed in internal front-end sessions. Eliminating legacy code and further improve code standards.

Full-stack Web Developer

Apr 2019 - Aug 2020

Bloomon

- Collaborating with designers to ensure designs were efficient and technically sound.
- Worked extensively with Product, Design and Engineering teams to ship multiple app-wide product features and improvements for feature gates, empty states, navigation, pricing, filters, actions, account etc.

Front-end Web Developer

May 2017 - Mar 2019

Famdy

- Built family tree platform with 4 team members using Vue and
- Integrated a token based authentication workflow for the SPA.
- Helped with rewriting the site for faster operation and code normalization.

Education

Bachelor's degree Dong Nai University 2010 - 2013

Personal details

Date of birth

December 3, 1992

Gender

Male

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/phi-khanhdo-353786248

Github

github.com/ngoisaomouoc

Skills

Javascript

Typescript

Vue.js

React

Angular

Node.js Quasar

Nuxt.js

Next.js

Laravel

Wordpress

HTML/CSS

Bootstrap/Tailwind CSS

SASS/SCSS

React native

Ionic

Languages

Vietnamese

English